Nadine C Paez Andrade

Nadine.paez1989@gmail.com 571-439-6828

OBJECTIVE:

To acquire a position within my chosen field that will challenge me and allow me to use my education, skills and past experiences in a way that is mutually beneficial to both myself and my employer and allow for future growth and advancement.

EDUCATION:

Full Stack Web Development - Bootcamp Certificate of Completion

February, 2022

George Washington University Proficiency gained in the following technologies:

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Express
- SQL
- MongoDB
- React

Acquired skills include:

- Build front-end websites from scratch, as well as using ready-made frameworks that allow efficiency
- Create full-stack single-page web applications using RESTful API routes and AJAX methods, and understand how front-end applications communicate with back-end applications and databases
- Implement structured and unstructured databases to convert static websites into dynamic websites that persist data
- Demonstrate string teamwork and project management skills as a collaborator and independent contributor during the development cycle of complex projects

Bachelor of Arts, Government and International Relations Minor in Intelligence Analysis

Graduation – magna cum laude George Mason University GPA 3.83/4.00 December 2017 Fairfax, VA

EXPERIENCE:

Reviewer II, Background Investigations

CACI International Inc.

January 2019 – July 2021 Chantilly, VA

- Created well-reasoned formal written documents for the government to make final adjudication decisions.
- Demonstrated a high level of personal integrity and the ability to discreetly handle sensitive information.
- Developed the ability to comprehend complex and multi-sourced data into concise and supportable final reports.
- Acquired thorough understanding of the federal rules and regulations that encompass and support the clearance process.
- Succeeded in operating various corporate and customer-specific automated systems for case tracking and status reporting.
- Demonstrated the ability to do the following: manage and prioritize multiple task assignments to meet deadlines, adapt to changing work requirements, provide on-the-job training to colleagues, and work in a fast-paced team environment.

EXPERIENCE:

Customer Account Representative DIRAK Inc.

June 2018 – Present Sterling, VA

- Aided in translating documents such as product descriptions from German to English
- Interacted with customers in a business setting via phone and email while prioritizing tasks and customer requests
- Reviewed and created documents such as Quote Requests, Purchase Orders, and other inquiries
- Handled Accounts Receivable high volume data entry
- Reviewed various reports such as aging receivables or backorders and reconciling accounts

Mobile Expert T-Mobile

April 2015 – Present Sterling, VA

- Experienced working in a goal driven environment while still maintaining high standards of customer service.
- Listened to and understood problems with customers' accounts and products while also providing solutions that enhanced their cellular experience and upgraded their accounts to offer maximum value.
- Followed up with customers through emails and calls. Contacted potential business and non-business customers to offer new products.

- Increased customer base by serving as an interpreter to promote various products to German speaking customers. Conducted consultation in German to secure the sale and satisfy customers' specific requests.
- Responsible for proper opening and closing procedures including securing merchandise and balancing registers and change-fund daily.

LANGUAGES

• German: fluent / fully proficient.

• Spanish: basic comprehension of language

AWARDS and SKILLS

- Dean's list (Fall 2016, Spring 2017, Fall 2017)
- Proficient with Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Navision
- Moderate proficiency in SPSS
- Moderate proficiency in SAP
- Strong interpersonal and analytical skills
- Developed a keen ability to pay attention to detail